[
    {
        "cell_ids": [
           2
        ],
        "question": "What are the three parts of the recommendation system designed in the notebook?",
        "answer": "Product popularity based system, Model-based collaborative filtering system, a search engine based recommendation system",
        "task": "Recommendation Systems",
        "skill": "Recommendation Systems"
    },
  {
        "cell_ids": [
            4
        ],
        "question": "What are the column names in the amazon ratings dataframe?",
        "answer": "UserId, ProductId, Rating, Timestamp",
        "task": "Basic Data Analysis",
        "skill": "Basic Data Analysis"
    },
    {
        "cell_ids": [
            4,
            5
        ],
        "question": "What is the shape of the original amazon ratings dataset?",
        "answer": "(2023070, 4)",
        "task": "Basic Data Analysis",
        "skill": "Basic Data Analysis"
    },
     {
        "cell_ids": [
            5
        ],
        "question": "What is the shape of the subset of the ratings dataset that is used (first 10000 rows)?",
        "answer": "(10000, 4)",
        "task": "Basic Data Analysis",
        "skill": "Basic Data Analysis"
    },
    {
        "cell_ids": [
            10
        ],
        "question": "What are the top 10 most popular products based on number of reviews?",
        "answer": "Based on the output provided in the notebook, they are: B001MA0QY2,B0009V1YR8,B0043OYFKU,B0000YUXI0,B003V265QW,B000ZMBSPE,B003BQ6QXK,B004OHQR1Q,B00121UVU0,B000FS05VG",
        "task":"Recommendation Systems",
        "skill": "Basic Data Analysis"
    },
    {
         "cell_ids": [
            15
         ],
         "question": "What is the predicted rating for movie id 872 by user id 3 using BaselineOnly algorithm?",
        "answer": "3.494574995057245",
        "task":"Recommendation Systems",
        "skill": "Collaborative Filtering"
    },
   {
        "cell_ids": [
            22
         ],
        "question": "What is the shape of the TF-IDF transformed matrix of product descriptions?",
       "answer": "(500, 8932)",
        "task": "Recommendation Systems",
         "skill": "Deep Neural Networks"
    },
   {
        "cell_ids": [
            25
         ],
         "question": "What are some of the top words in cluster 0 of product descriptions?",
        "answer": " concrete, stake, ft, coating, apply, epoxy, drying, sq, garage, formula",
         "task": "Recommendation Systems",
         "skill": "Deep Neural Networks"
    },
    {
        "cell_ids": [
            27
        ],
        "question": "Based on the clustering model, which cluster does the 'cutting tool' keyword belong to?",
        "answer": "Cluster 4",
        "task":"Recommendation Systems",
        "skill": "Deep Neural Networks"
    },
      {
        "cell_ids": [
           28
        ],
        "question": "Based on the clustering model, which cluster does the 'spray paint' keyword belong to?",
          "answer": "Cluster 2",
        "task":"Recommendation Systems",
        "skill": "Deep Neural Networks"
    }
]